now go back to talking about the tried
and true one that I was going to talk
about before um a imbd for politicians
not called ped of course I just like
using existing ideas you like how great
will this work for I mean I don't care
so much about actors and actresses I do
like the fact that I can find out when I
see someone where I knew them from very
easily but for politicians I want to be
able to know what they stand for and not
just what they say during the platform
and the partners are getting elected I
want to know what there's what they've
actually voted on in the past what their
employment history is well who they get
money from and as it grows and our base
grows it becomes a platform to have a
conversation with them where we're
easily able to say what's your stance on
the topics that they don't talk about
and they can say no comments but then
they actually have to say no comment so
I'm just not going to tell you my stance
on abortion and I'm just not going to so
at least no comment is still something
they can't just completely ignore it and
not have people know so so yeah the more
the bigger any of these get the more
power that we have as a membership-based
to have them be even more powerful so a
whole number 49 is political a
politician imbd